Italy
Marist College
Italy
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.2.6
1203 Linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Glass plate negatives; Italy
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass plate negatives, 2.1.1
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - Italy, 2.1.1.2.6
              - Lowell Thomas and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas eating at table, 1917 1918; 49 (Box 1323)
                3.5x4.5
              - Lowell Thomas and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas eating at table, looking at camera, 1917 1918; 50
              - Lowell Thomas and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas standing in street, looking at each other, 1917 1918; 51
              - Lowell Thomas and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at the Trevi Fountain in Rome, Italy, 1917 1918; 52
              - Lowell Thomas and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas outside a building talking to soldiers, 1917 1918; 53
              - Lowell Thomas and two other men in front of planes, looking at camera, 1917 1918; 54
              - Lowell Thomas standing with many military men outside a building, 1917 1918; 55
                4x5
              - Lowell Thomas in automobile with soldiers driving past soldiers on horses, 1917 1918; 56
                film
              - Lowell Thomas and many military men standing in street, 1917 1918; 57
              - Lowell Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi drinking outside a café, 1917 1918; 58
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi at the Ponte Vechio, 1917 1918; 59
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at the Trevi Fountain, 1917 1918; 60
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi talking with three soldiers in front of large building, 1917 1918; 61
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas talking to two women and man, 1917 1918; 62
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas talking to two women and man, 1917 1918; 63
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas talking to man and woman, 1917 1918; 64
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi in car, two military men in front seat, 1917 1918; 65
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in parked car next to river, 1917 1918; 66
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas standing with military man, looking at nearby airplanes, 1917 1918; 67
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and a military man in front of airplane, 1917 1918; 68
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi in automobile, 1917 1918; 69
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi stand on bridge over canal, Venice, 1917 1918; 70
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas along riverside, close-up, 1917 1918; 71
              - Lowell Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi standing amid ruins of coliseum, 1918; 1 (Box 1323)
              - Military battery, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas at left with back to camera, 1918; 2
              - Frances Ryan Thomas on Piave front, 1918; 3
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas standing in field looking at a church in ruins, 1918; 4
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Harry G. Thomas standing on bridge in Florence, Italy, Ponte Vecchio in background, 1918; 5
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas standing in doorway of train, 1918; 6
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas standing on sidewalk, 1918; 7
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, portrait in front of building, 1918; 8
              - Portrait of Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas sitting down, 1918; 9
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas standing in distance in St. Peter’s Square, Vatican City, 1918; 10
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas talking to the Prince of Wales, other soldiers scattered, 1918; 11
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas talking to soldier in courtyard of the American Red Cross, 1918; 12
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas kneeling down, feeding many pigeons, 1918; 13
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, standing up, feeding pigeons, 1918; 14
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in gondola in Venice, 1918; 15
              - Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, and Harry G. Thomas in front of St. Peter’s Cathedral in Vatican City, 1918; 16
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Harry G. Thomas sitting at restaurant table, eating, 1918; 17
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Harry G. Thomas sitting at a restaurant table, eating, 1918; 18
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Harry G. Thomas sitting at restaurant table, 1918; 19
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Harry G. Thomas talking to others on street, 1918; 20
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Harry G. Thomas talking to others on street, 1918; 21
              - Harry G. Thomas talking to two others on street, 1918; 22
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas talking to Luisa Tetrazzini outside automobile, 1918; 23
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi surrounded by birds, 1918; 24
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi speaking to soldiers at the Red Cross, 1918; 25
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi facing each other, 1918; 26
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas climbing into gondola with the help of Major Piero Tozzi, 1918; 27
              - Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Luisa Tetrazzini standing on steps of large building, 1918; 28
              - Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas and Luisa Tetrazzini standing on steps of large building next to automobile, 1918; 29
              - Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, Major Piero Tozzi, and Luisa Tetrazzini standing in front of Silvering fountain, 1918; 30
              - Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, Major Piero Tozzi and Luisa Tetrazzini sitting at table, smiling, 1918; 31
              - Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Luisa Tetrazzini talking at outdoor table, 1918; 32
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, Major Piero Tozzi, and Luisa Tetrazzini at outdoor table, looking at each other, 1918; 33
              - Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi at outdoor table, 1918; 34
              - Elaborate building with small pool in front, people on sidewalk, 1918; 35
              - Six men standing in front of mountains, lined up, looking at camera, Adamello, Italy, 1918; 36
              - Man and woman sitting at table, outside house covered with vines, woman feeding man, 1918; 37
              - Man and woman standing outside house, looking up, 1918; 38
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas in a building with large columns, 1918; 39
                1.5x3
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi talking to a woman and man in front of trees, 1918; 40
                2.25x3.5
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi talking to a man and woman in front of trees, 1918; 41
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Major Piero Tozzi standing amid ruins, 1918; 42
                2x3
              - Small dome building behind columns in ruins, 1918; 43
              - St. Peter’s Square, fountain, Vatican City, 1918; 44
                3.5x4.25
              - St. Peter’s Square, crowd of people near columns, Vatican City, 1918; 45
              - Obelisk in the Piazza de Popolo, Rome, 1918; 46
              - Fountain of the Naiads, Piazza della Repubblica, Rome, 1918; 47
              - Street scene, Florence Duomo in distance, Florence, 1918; 48
              - Baptistery of the Cathedral of Pisa, Leaning Tower of Pisa in distance, 1918; 49
                5x7
              - Street scene, Verona clock tower in distance, Verona, 1918; 50
              - Doge’s Palace, Venice, 1918; 51
              - Doge’s Palace, distant view, Venice, 1918; 52
              - Gondola, Basilica Di San Marcos in distance, Venice, 1918; 53
              - Docked boats, Basilica Di San Marcos, in distance at left, bell tower of St. Mark’s Square in distance at right, Venice, 1918; 54
              - Street scene along waterfront, bell tower of St. Mark’s Square in distance, Venice, 1918; 55
              - Rialto Bridge, two women and a man walking along canal, Venice, 1918; 56
              - Ornate building near small bridge, Venice, 1918; 57
              - Buildings along canal, two boats in foreground, Venice, 1918; 58
              - Gondolas, people talking along street, Venice, 1918; 59
              - Hotel Europe, Venice, 1918; 60
              - Grand Canal Hotel and waterfront buildings, Venice, 1918; 61
              - Man wearing suit standing next to canal, Venice, 1918; 62
              - Street scene, statue of a lion in foreground, 1918; 63
              - Street scene, laundry hanging from balcony, 1918; 64
              - Two men standing with carriage outside Hotel Pension Pincio, Italy [?], 1918; 65
              - Two men, one pointing at poster for “La Vedova Allegra” at American Kursaal, 1918; 66
              - Men standing next to columns, 1918; 67
              - Crowd of people near ornate building with arch and sign for the American Red Cross, 1918; 68
              - Ornate arch with many statues, Italy [?], 1918; 69
              - Woman holding broom, standing next to statue, Italy [?], 1918; 70
              - Two men in military uniforms surrounded by tall buildings, 1918; 71
              - Large group watching men on balcony of American Red Cross, 1918; 72
              - Military men walking in square, American Red Cross in distance, 1918; 73